Guide to the Dan Nimrod papers, 1938-2002 MS2192
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Correspondence - United States, 1956-2002; MS2192 Series 5; 10.5 Linear feet
  - Sakier, A.H., 05/01/1979-02/19/1981 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Sauna, Victor (prof - St. John's University), 07/06/1982-01/19/1990 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Schechter, E. (dr), 01/10/1981-11/01/1983 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Schleicher, Jerry, 11/24/1980-09/17/1981 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Schlesinger, Alex, 09/09/1980-09/20/1985 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Schwartz, Samuel (rabbi - Congregation Beth Jacob), 03/06/1980-11/20/1981 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Schweig, Serena M., 03/12/1981-08/27/1982 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Setlow, Herbert D., 05/08/1978-05/21/1978 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Shaller, Moshe, 05/22/1984-03/10/1985 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Shalom International - Eiklor, Frank (dr), 01/19/1989-01/03/1997 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Shengold Properties - Sheinbaum, Moshe, 04/08/1983-05/21/1986 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Shofar Association of America, 01/27/1980-11/19/1984 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Shulman, Richard H., 11/17/1991-01/21/1999 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Simon-Steiner, Elsie, 09/21/1981-07/26/1985 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Smertenko (prof), 08/20/1980-11/30/1980 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Southgate, Minoo (prof - Baruch College - City University of N.Y.), 02/14/1992-03/02/1992 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Special Interest A-H, 1978-2002 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    [from contents page of folder:] Abraham Fund; Abraham Press; Action for Soviet Jewry; Alexander, Edward (prof); Aliyah Movement (North American); AMEN Publishing Company; American & Canadian Coptic Association; American Interfaith Institute; Amkraut, David & Associates; Atlantic Jewish Council; Baker, Nathan; Bama ale; Baron, Jeffrey; Barsel, Uriah; Barskey, Neil; Bat Kol - A Feminist House of Study; Ben-Tovin, Noah; Beres, Louis-Rene; Blatt, David L.; Berkower, Morris; Bloch, David; Blue Light Films; Bomzer, Herbert (rabbi); Bookazine Company Inc.; Book Mania Inc.; Bortnick, Samuel; Bowher, R.R. Data Collection Center; Brandeis University - Reisman, Bernard; Brynford Bible Church; Burt, Mark; Bussel, Deborah; Central Agency for Jewish Education; Christian Copts of California; Classic Printers; Committee of Jewish Family Purity; Concern for Israel; Creative Media; Dannhauser, Werner; Dashe, Lewis; Davis, Alex (rabbi); Delaney, James; Directory of American Jewish Organizations; Dobin, Rubin (rabbi); Dreyfus, Marion; Dub, Karen; Embassy of Costa Rica; Eris, Alfred; Estershon, A.J.; Family Protection Scoreboard; Foreign Policy; Forester, Arnold; Forward; Freiwald, Milton; Frenkel, Dan; Friedman, Sigmund; Friends of Israel Gospel Ministry Inc.; Gaibel, Zalman; Garden, Martin; Glick, Edward; Golden, Lou; Goldstein, Daniel; Gordon, Louis A.; Green, Elliot; Grossman, Sylvia; Guttman, Sharon; Hebrew Union College; Herschaft, Randy; Hess, William; Hilberg, Rauol (prof); Hirschler, Gertrude; Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace; Horney, Frank; Horowitz, A. (rabbi); Horwitz, Chaim
  - Special Interest I-Q, 1978-1996 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    [from contents page in folder:] Information regarding Israel Security (IRIS); Isaacs, Daniel F.; Israel Action Committee; Jacobovits, Joshua; Jaffa, Harry V. (prof); Jewish Community of Hebron; Jungreis, Esther; Kahun, Tillie; Kahl, Murray; Kalkstein, Howard; Katsh, Abraham (prof); Kessler, Max P.; Kimmel, Bernard (rabbi, dr); Kissel, Phyllis Marie Sarah; Klurman, Aba & Zisi; Koch, L. (Rt. Hon.); Korenstein, Antony; Krakow, David; Kunin, Myron; Kwas, Mark; Largy, Ed; Latz, Arje; Lederer, Norman; Lerman, Alice C.; Life Messengers; Lishkas Ezras Achim; Lustick, I. (prof); Maccabeeyah de Hashmoniyim; Medi-Fund Inc.; Mehlan, W.; Meiselman, Winnie; Meyerson, N. (dr); Michael, Amnon; Middle East Christians Committee (MECHRIC); Solomonow, Allan; Nagelbush Realty; Negrin, Milton; New York, City of; New York Times; News World Communications Inc.; Oakland, Beatrice; Opalek, A. (dr); Operation Truth; Ozick, Cynthia; Peck, Arlene G.; Peters, Joan; Pincus, Gaula; Prism Entertainment; Quinlan, James P.
  - Special Interest R-Z, 1977-1999 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    [from contents page of folder:] R.K. Associates; Rabinovitch, Flora; Raynold, Alexander; Reilly, Robert R.; Republican National Committee; Ritman, Lawrence H.; Rosen, Philip (dr); Rivkin, Sholom (rabbi); Rosengard, Andrea; Rosner, Helen; Ross, Norman; Rossberg, Ellin; Roumani, Maurice (dr); Rottenberg, Isaac C.; Rutgers University; Saar, Ed.; Sable, Martin H. (dr); Samet, Lee; Schactman, Irving; Schechter, Erik; Scholem, David; Schuchmann, Mary; Schwartz, Jacques; Schweig, Edwin Stephen; Sephardic Studies Program; Shapolsky, Ian; Shimon, B.; Sidor, Bronislaw; Silverman, Joel P. (M.D.); Simon, Gerald; Simon Wisenthal Center; Snyder, Steven; Solzhenitsyn, Alexander; Spanel, A.N.; Spector, Gerald; Speilberg, Steven; Starkman, Jay; Steiner, Elise Simon; Stillman, Morris; Strager, Avren; Strober, Gerald S.; Stupnitzki, M.; Teitelbaum, M.J.; Tov Moshe Ish; Tuchman, Barbara; University of Alabama; Victims of Arab Terror; Virnick, Rachmeil; Wallach, Howard; Warren, Robert; Warren, Sol; Weiner, Gordon M. (prof); Weintraub Gallery; Weiss, Jerold; White, A. Rebecca; Wolk, Rochelle Saidel; Segal, I.B.; Zimmerman, M.; Zion, Sidney; Zussman, Herbert L. (dr); Zweibon, Herbert
  - Spektor, Eryk, 10/11/1979-12/15/1980 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Stokes, W.E.D. (jr), 08/19/1983-10/21/1984 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Sturm, Edward (prof) 1982, 02/18/1982-12/22/1982 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Sturm, Edward (prof) 1983-1986, 01/16/1983-12/30/1986 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Sturm, Edward (prof) 1987-2000, 01/04/1987-06/13/2000 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Taitel, Irving, 01/30/1981-10/12/1987 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Teichberg, Ignatius, 09/04/1980-10/16/1981 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Topas, George, 05/13/1984-08/28/2000 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Torczyner, Jacques, 04/06/1982-09/1996 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Towards Tradition - Lapin, Daniel (rabbi), 03/23/1995-03/29/1995 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Trachtenberg, Stephen Joel (dr Prof GWU) 1985-1998, 07/02/1985-12/16/1998 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Trachtenberg, Stephen Joel (dr Prof GWU) Jan-May 1999, 01/06/1999-05/28/1999 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Trachtenberg, Stephen Joel (dr Prof GWU) Jun-Dec 1999, 06/07/1999-12/28/1999 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Trachtenberg, Stephen Joel (dr Prof GWU) Jan-Jun 2000, 01/10/2000-06/30/2000 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Trachtenberg, Stephen Joel (dr Prof GWU) Jul-Dec 2000, 07/10/2000-12/27/2000 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Trachtenberg, Stephen Joel (dr Prof GWU) 2001, 03/07/2001-05/15/2001 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Tsomet Techiya - USA, 08/05/1986 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - United States Department of State, 11/19/1983-04/11/1989 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - United States Senators, Congressmen - anti-Israel, 11/11/1981-01/16/1987 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    Title of the folder is Nimrod's original.
  - Union of Orthodox Jewish Congregations of America - Stolper, Pinchas (rabbi), 07/30/1979-01/20/1982 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Vaksman, Fabian, 03/26/1991-03/29/1996 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Van Impe, Jack, 02/16/1981-12/02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Weintraub, Robert - The Stepping Stone Fund, 07/31/1979-07/07/1993 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - White House, the - Washington, 05/05/1981-11/19/1983 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Weisel, Elie (prof), 08/02/1977-04/20/1985 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Wilstein Institute of Jewish Policy Studies - Wilstein, Susan & David, 05/08/1991-08/28/1992 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Winston, Emanuel A., 03/22/1982-06/20/2000 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Wisenberg, Herbert esq & Milfred, 06/17/1945-12/07/1989 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Wisse, Ruth (prof - Harvard (McGill)), 09/30/1980-01/02/2001 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Wijnen, Janice 1986-1997, 11/1983-09/28/1997 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Wijnen, Janice 1998-2002, 01/09/1998-01/10/2002 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Wolfson Family Foundation Inc., 12/01/1980-08/24/1982 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - World Habeas Corpus - Kutner, Luis Jan-Mar 1982, 01/19/1982-03/25/1982 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - World Habeas Corpus - Kutner, Luis Apr 1982-1983, 04/01/1982-04/23/1983 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - World Habeas Corpus - Kutner, Luis 1984-Feb 1987, 02/08/1984-02/17/1987 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - World Habeas Corpus - Kutner, Luis Mar-Dec 1987, 03/04/1987-11/30/1987 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - World Lebanese Organization (W.L.O.), 09/08/1993 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - World Media Conference, 08/20/1983-12/15/1987 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - World Organization of Jews from Arab Countries (W.O.J.A.C.) - Haddad, Herskel (dr), 03/31/1992-03/30/1993 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - World Union Press - Horowitz, David, 03/24/1980-09/26/1980 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Young Israel of Hollywood-Fort Lauderdale Inc. - Davis, Edward (rabbi), 08/18/1986-08/11/1987 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Zimmerman, Michael, 07/23/1980-11/17/1994 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Zionist Archives & Library, 08/09/1978-04/21/1985 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Zionist Organization of America (Z.O.A.) - National Head Office, 05/15/1978-10/29/1995 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Zionist Organization of America (Z.O.A.) Regional Offices, 1982-2000 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    [from contents page of folder:] New England Region, Boston, Mass. / C. Kruss / S. Manski; Pennsylvania; Pittsburgh Zionist District, Pitts., PA. / Michael A. Bierman; San Francisco District, S.F., CA. / Lucie Ramsey
- Correspondence - Other Countries, 1974-2002; MS2192 Series 6; 3 Linear feet
  This series contains Nimrod's correspondence with people and organizations in other countries besides those in Series 1-5. The material dates from 1974-2002. Some of the material is in French. It includes correspondence with individuals and organizations in Australia, Belgium, Czechoslovakia (now the Czech Republic and Slovakia), France, Ghana, Greece, Holland (the Netherlands), Hong Kong, India, Ireland, Italy, various countries of Latin America, Malta, Mexico, Moldova Republic, New Zealand, Nigeria, the Philippines, South Africa, Spain, Switzerland, Turkey, and Zambia. The South Africa section contains copies of the Aida Parker Newsletter, from a prominent conservative activist and correspondent of Nimrod. This series is sorted by country, and within each country in alphabetical order by correspondent, then chronologically within each folder. Folders labeled "Special Interest," "Archives & Libraries," and "Archives - Libraries - Research Institutes" contain multiple correspondents, sorted alphabetically within those folders.
  - Archives & Libraries - Australia, 04/20/1979 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Australian Jewish News, 02/02/1979-12/02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Australian Jewry - Executive Council - Leibler, Isi, 08/12/1980-12/02/1999 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - David Press (The) - Australia, 06/16/1981-11/04/1992 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Healy, A.N. (dr) - University of Wollongong - Australia, 05/29/1980-09/05/1980 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Herut Zionist Revisionist - Dreyer, Hans - Australia, 01/02/1979-09/02/1985 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Jewish Board of Deputies - Jones, Jeremy - Australia, 11/20/1985-12/16/1985 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Jewish Commentary - Braham, Mark - Australia, 01/14/1985-12/01/1998 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - J.I.P. - (Jordan is Arab Palestine) - Singer, D. - Australia, 12/02/1981-04/14/1987 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Kemelman, Y. (rabbi, dr) - Australia, 01/03/1979-01/28/1982 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Klinger, M. - Australia, 05/29/1978-07/26/1985 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Neustein, Janet & Michael - Australia, 03/25/1982-06/04/1983 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Rubinstein, W.D. (prof Deakin University) - Australia, 08/24/1979-07/02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Scott-Young, H. (Rev.) - Australia, 02/10/1982-04/06/1982 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Special Interest - Australia, 1978-1990 (Box 12, Folder 85)
    [from contents page of folder:] Angus & Robertson; Australian Worker's Union; Bindon, Thomas J.; Cohen, Lex (dr); Edwards, Russell K. (dr); Fitzgerald, Anthony B.; Harris, Nathan; Jabotinsky, Bet; Meschers, Emmanuel; Robin White Books; Schneeweiss, Joachim (dr); Skall, E.
  - Special Interest - Belgium, 1978-1985 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    [from contents page of folder:] Abramowicz, G.; A.S.B.L.; Eched, Samuel; Solidarite avec Israel
  - Special Interest - Czechoslovakia, 12/14/1992 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    [from contents page of folder:] Zidovska nabozenska obec v Praze
  - Archives / Libraries / Research Institutes / Misc. - France, 04/03/1980 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    [from contents page of folder:] Centre de Documentation Juive Contemporaire
  - Finch, Scot - France, 05/04/1987-03/04/1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Franz Israel Information - Reiter, Alexandre - France, 08/06/1979-10/28/1984 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Grad, A.D. (dr) - France, 07/03/1980-04/16/1982 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Herut-Hatzohar - Betar/Tagar - Kupfer, Jacques - Zionist Revisionists - France, 03/11/1993 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Labin, Suzanne (dr) - France, 07/08/1980-12/15/1981 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Soustelle, Jacques - France, 12/11/1984-11/23/1988 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Special Interest - France, 1978-1989 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    [from contents page of folder:] Bensoussan, E. (rabbi); Calef, Michel; Dreyfus, H.; Grad, A.D.; Figaro (le); Hajdenberg, Henri (dr); Nahon, Gerard - Societe des etudes juives; Pisar, Samuel (attorney); Stara, A.; Tribune Juive; Vitenberg, Jacques (dr)
  - Special Interest - Ghana, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    [from contents page of folder:] Classic Printers Limited
  - Special Interest - Greece, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    [from contents page of folder:] Emmanouil, Ilias; Tarfon, Avraam
  - Herut Hatzohar - Zionist Revisionist 1978-1981 - Holland, 07/23/1978-12/07/1981 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Herut Hatzohar - Zionist Revisionist - 1982-1985 - Holland, 02/08/1982-07/26/1985 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Special Interest - Holland, 1979-2000 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    [from contents page of folder:] Baruch, J.Z. (dr); Israeli, J.; Nederlands Genootschap Library; Swart, B.; Swets Blackwell
  - Special Interest - Hong Kong, 1980-1989 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    [from contents page of folder:] Liberman, Jack; South China Morning Post
  - Special Interest - India, 04/02/1988 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    [from contents page of folder:] Yehudi, Prem Doss S. (Advocat)
  - Harris, Monte 1974-1978 - Ireland, 01/15/1974-12/31/1978 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Harris, Monte 1979-1981 - Ireland, 01/29/1979-05/26/1981 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Harris, Monte / Charters, David (dr) - Conflict Quarterly - Ireland, 02/18/1978-04/13/1978 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Special Interest - Ireland, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    [from contents page of folder:] Gilbert, J.Z. (Mrs.); Tash Inc.
  - Fabrovitch, Louisa - Italy, 02/03/1997-04/04/2000 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Gerhardinger, Rodolfo & Virginia - Italy, 03/10/1990-08/11/1999 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Pietrobon, Paola & Bruno - Italy, 04/06/1999-02/05/2001 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Special Interest - Italy, 1980-1986 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    [from contents page of folder:] Dal Monte, Giulio; Prioli, Tullio; Unione Tipografico
  - Zanardo, Francesco - Italy, 12/1998-10/26/2000 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Special Interest - Latin America, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    [from contents page of folder:] Argentina: Federacion de Communidades Israelitas Argentinas; Brazil: Universidade de Sao Paolo; Venezuela: Goldman, Carlos (dr); Laufer, Hose
  - Micallef, Lino 1981-1982 - Malta, 02/21/1981-11/15/1982 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Micallef, Lino 1983-1989 - Malta, 01/10/1983-12/05/1989 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Micallef, Lino 1990-1997 - Malta, 02/10/1990-03/11/1997 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Glik Communicacion, S.A. - Mexico, 04/03/1983-07/13/1984 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Special Interest - Mexico, 1978-1983 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    [from contents page of folder:] Centro Deportivo Israelita; Delgadillo, Luisa Martinez; Embajada de Israel; WIZO
  - Gabinsky, M.A. 1992-1994 - Moldova Republic, 06/21/1992-11/13/1994 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Gabinsky, M.A. 1995-2000 - Moldova Republic, 02/20/1995-03/28/2000 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - McCormick, John B. - New Zealand, 01/22/1980-01/11/1984 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Special Interest - New Zealand, 1980-1989 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    [from contents page of folder:] Bennett, Paul; International Christian Embassy; Octopus Publishing Group Ltd.
  - Nieketien, Andrew - Nigeria, 10/21/1984-10/26/1987 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Special Interest - Philippines, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    [from contents page of folder:] Dayot, Ernesto J.
  - Babb, Glenn (hon) - South Africa, 11/06/1989-06/12/1990 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Blumenthal, Yedidiah 1978-1985 - South Africa, 03/27/1978-12/16/1985 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Blumenthal, Yedidiah 1986-1992 - South Africa, 02/05/1986-12/07/1992 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Blumenthal, Yedidiah 1993-2001 (Undated material) - South Africa, 01/25/1993-04/25/1997 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Christian Action for Israel - South Africa (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Jewish Affairs - South Africa, 01/01/1980-09/06/1993 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Parker, Aida 1989-1990 - South Africa, 04/16/1989-12/15/1990 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Parker, Aida 1991-1992 - South Africa, 01/03/1991-12/02/1992 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Parker, Aida 1993-1994 - South Africa, 01/27/1993-12/12/1994 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Parker, Aida 1995-1997 - South Africa, 01/31/1995-12/26/1997 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Parker, Aida 1998-2002 (Undated material) - South Africa, 01/28/1998-05/30/2002 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Rosenberg, H.A. - South Africa, 08/21/1978-09/21/1982 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Sharon, M. (prof) - South Africa, 08/25/1986-12/04/1986 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Special Interest - South Africa, 1980-1989 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    [from contents page of folder:] African Jewish Newspaper; Jordan is Arab Palestine; Klugman, H.B. (dr); Sanclip-Werner, Gil
  - Special Interest - Spain, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    [from contents page of folder:] Benbunan, Moises (dr)
  - Affolter, Emmi - Switzerland, 11/08/1985-11/15/2000 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Beth-Shalom - Switzerland, 07/03/1979-02/19/1981 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Botshko, Moche (rabbi) - Switzerland, 10/27/1980-12/01/1980 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Cohn, Arthur - Switzerland, 04/15/1980-10/28/1984 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Special Interest - Switzerland, 1979-1998 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    [from contents page of folder:] Bank Julius Baer & Co. A.G.; Bloch, J.P.; Sigg, Albertine; World Jewish Congress
  - Special Interest - Turkey, 1980-1992 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    [from contents page of folder:] Celalyan, Vartuhi - Jamanak, Editor; Metin, Burhan - Perspektif, General Director
  - Special Interest - Zambia, 02/27/1984 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    [from contents page of folder:] University of Zambia
- Biographical Information - Prominent Correspondents, MS2192 Series 7; 1.5 Linear feet
  This series contains short biographical sketches of some of Nimrod's more prominent correspondents, and also of Israeli cabinet officials in the 1980s. Some are photocopies of autobiographies, others are official biographies of individuals, and some are biographies written by Nimrod to accompany his mailings of these individuals' writings.
  - Biographies A-F (Box 13, Folder 61)
    Contains biographical information on the following [from contents page of folder]: Meir Abelson; Dr. Martin Abend; Prof. Edward Alexander; Moshe Arens; Yedidya Atlas, journalist; Marc Samuel Baker; Louis N. Balcher; Sandra Oster Baras, attorney; Yehudit Barsky, senior analyst; Parry R. Bellot; Yitshaq Ben-Ami; Shifra Blass, teacher; Mel Borenstein, businessman; Charles David Brooks; Bobby Brown, mayor of Tekoa; Rep. Tom Corcoran; Alan Cornet; Jim Courter, representative; Barbara DeKovner-Mayer; Arye D'eri; Rafael Eitan; Ya'acov Eliav (Levstein); Yoram Ettinger, consul general; Rev. Jerry Falwell; Prof. Harold Fisch; Paul Flacks; Avigail Frij, political scientist
  - Biographies G-M (Box 13, Folder 62)
    Contains biographical information on the following [from contents page of item 00061]: Peter E. Goldman; Rabbi Shlomo Goren; Ben Tzion Greenberger, deputy mayor Maale Adumim; Eliyakim Ha'etzni, esq.; Zevulun Hammer; Yisrael Harel, chairman of the Yesha Council; Yehoshafat Harkabi, former head of Israeli military intelligence; Monte Harris; Yoram Hazony, Ph.D.; Richard A. Hellman; Datya Herkovitz, spokeswoman for the Gaza council; Shifra Hoffman; Leonard Horwin, esq.; Rael Jean Isaac, Ph.D.; Vladimir Jabotinsky; Dr. Jan Karski; Shmuel Katz; Moshe Katzav; Ruth King; Dr. Charles H. Kremer; Luis Kutner, esq.; Suzanne Labin, Ph.D.; Bob Lang, spokesman for the Yesha council; Mark Langfan, esq.; Prof Yeshayahn Leibowitz; Yechiel M. Leiter, exec. director of Yesha council's foreign desk, rabbi; David Levy; Al Liss; David Magen; Marvin Maurer; Donald McAlvany; Yisrael Medad, mayor of Shiloh; Dan Meridor; Roni Milo; Yitzhak Moda'i; Prof. Sol Modell; William Morrisey; Dr. Irving Moskowitz; Boris Mukhametshin
  - Biographies N-S (Box 13, Folder 63)
    Contains biographical information on the following [from contents page of item 00061]: Yitzchak Navon; Yuval Ne'eman; Deputy Ambassador Benjamin Netanyahu; Dr. Mordechai Nisan; Moshe Nissim; Barbara Oberman, Public Relations Consultant; Ehud Olmert; Gideon Patt; Yitzhak Haim Peretz; Joan Peters; Rafael Pinhasi; Dr. Roland I. Pritikin (M.D.), Col.; Joseph Puder; Rabbi Emanuel Rackman; Shaul Ramati, amb. (ret.); Aaron Israel Reichel, esq.; Dr. Paul Riebenfeld; Ambassador Ernesto Rivas-Gallont; Philip Rosen, Ph.D.; Gershon Salomon; Dr. Edward Schechter; Alexander Schlesinger; Geraldine J. Schwartz, Ph.D.; Dina Shalit, assistant to the mayor of Ariel; Moshe Shamir, member of Knesset; Yitzhak Shamir; Ariel Sharon, member of Knesset; Ora Shem-Ur, author/journalist; Rita Simon, Ph.D.; Eric H. Sontag; Axel (Caesar) Springer
  - Biographies T-Z (& additional shorts) (Box 13, Folder 64)
    Contains biographical information on the following [from contents page of item 00061]: Paul Trepman; Ben Weider; Daniella Weiss; Rabbi Julian M. White; Maxine Wolf; L. Marc Zell, esq.; Herbert Zweibon; [additional biographical shorts:] Bama'ale: Prof. Y. Ben-Shlomo; E. Haetzni, Adv.; S. Katz; Prof. Y. Neiman, M.K.; Dr. M. Nisan; Minister A. Sharon, M.K.; Rabbi E. Waldman, M.K.; D. Weiss; Dr. Z. Yeivan; [BESA Research Associates:] Prof. Efraim Inbar, Ph.D.; Prof. Stuart A. Cohen, Ph.D.; Dr. Gil Feiler, Ph.D.; Prof. Eliyahu Kanovsky, Ph.D.; Prof. Aharon Klieman, Ph.D.; Dr. Anat Lapidot, Ph.D.; Dr. Amikam Nachmani, Ph.D.; Prof. Shmuel Sandler, Ph.D.; Dr. Dany Shohan, Ph.D.; Dr. Gerald M. Steinberg, Ph.D.
  - Credential for organizations (Box 13, Folder 65)
    [from contents page of folder]: Americans for a Safe Israel Inc. (AFSI); Americans for Undivided Israel; American Jewish Coalition; The American Jewish Year Book; The Anne Frank Institute of Philadelphia; BESA Center for Strategic Studies; BETAR USA; Committee for Accuracy in Middle East Reporting in America (CAMERA); Common Ground; Dawn Publishing Company Ltd.; Facts and Logic about the Middle East (FLAME); France-Israel; Freeman Center for Strategic Studies; Friends of Jerusalem Temple Mount, Inc.; Herut-Hatzohar, World Union of; International Jewish Correspondence (I.J.C.); International Relations Task Force; Israel Bulletin; The Jerusalem Institute for Western Defense; Jewish Action Initiative (JAI); The Jewish Right; Jordan Is Palestine Committee (N.Y.) (J.I.P.); Magen David Adom (M.D.A.); Mideast Mirror; Moledet; PELI (Pe'ilim Lema'an Eretz Yisrael); Pro Israel Inc.; The Promised Land; Quebec-Israel Committee (QIC); Sanclip (Southern Africa Newsclipping Service); Saturday Night; School for Overseas Students Mt. Scopus; The Shalem Center; Techiya, U.S.A.; Victims of Arab Terror International, Inc. (VAT); The Wilstein Institute; World Habeas Corpus; World Media Association; YESHA Council
- Publications, 1959-2002; MS2192 Series 8; 5 Linear feet